Suddenly Explorers! I'm Yuuki Taguchi and Shinki Yoshida!
We are Yuuki Taguchi and Shinki Yoshida! Please!
Please! We are the "Suddenly Explorers"!
Today we have these two.
Isn't this your first time? This fair.
Ah! That's it! We won an award!
That's it! Congratulations!
Kikutani Bookstore!
Congratulations!
That's great, isn't it!
Is it still on display?
They are still on display!
Please go check it out!
There's the award-winning one!
So, what are they going to do for us today?
What will they be doing today?
Touch them and you're dead!
You've already done it!
No, I haven't. Not yet.
I haven't done it yet.
You should do it.
This is the second time we've had the Bricko Expedition.
Normally, we have everyone explore the E Beans building with just the bare bones.
To further promote E Beans to the world
We decided to make them even cuter.
So today, we're going to have the two of you explore the museum as if you were Britto.
Can you do that? Can you do it?
Kitami, are you okay?
I'm already doing it!
I'm in!
You're good at that.
Actually, you're good at it. Kitami-san.
And now, let me tell you where I want you to go exploring in that bling.
Today's exploration is
Let me introduce you to Dio Cheese's 10-yen bread.
The 10-yen bread has already been a hot topic on sns, etc., and it has just landed in Sendai for the first time!The 10-yen bread that has already been a hot topic on sns and other social media is now in eFutozu, or rather, it has landed in Sendai for the first time.
It's now at the front entrance of the first floor of e-futozu, in a kitchen car.
I'm going to introduce you to the 10-yen bread today as if I were Bricko.
Good night, Mr. Ohkun.
Good night.
Hey, hey, which way is it?
Which way is it? What shall we do?
I don't know, Shinju-chan.
Then let's eat 10 yen bread together!
Yay! Now there's a hot item.
Hey, let's have 10 yen and 80 yen bread.
Wow, I'm excited!
What? Where's the store?
Anpanman!
I'm a slow runner.
I'm not making any progress.
What? Why is that?
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck, too.
I want to go.
Let's see...
It says something about...
Please make your purchase in 15 minutes.
Please don't point at me.
If you attack
Death
I'm stuck!
Embarrassing
The cheese is too big!
He said it'll make it impossible to fly.
I've got to eat it.
But I'm a slow eater.
You want to order?
Let's order.
Excuse me.
Can I have a 10-Yen Tang, please?One ten-yen tang, please.
Thank you very much.
One more, please.
Another one?
Yes, two in total?
Yes, sir.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Yay! I got my first errand.
Let's turn around and go.
Yes!
It's okay!
Jansen Sen Hui!
Look away!
I've lost!
Yeah!
Let's go, extra!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're the favorite!
Whoo!
Here we go!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Take care, everyone.
Hot, hot, hot.
Hot. Hot.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
As big as blue, bigger than my hair
You want some?
Yes, let's eat over there.
Okay, okay.
Ready, eat!
Look at that.
So cute.cute
in front of
Look at that!
Amazing!
Oh, yummy! Oh, choo choo choo!
Wow, they're so good, I'll go on and on.
It's like candy again!
Okay, it's hot, so I'm going to make a poo-poo.
Okay, here we go.
Candy!
Candy.
Mwah.
Mmm.
Very tasty.
Are you okay?
It's the same time. I'm a little star player now.
That was close.
Se...
Okay.
Here you go.
Bon appétit!
Se-no!
Yum!
Delicious!
Mmmmmm!
It's good, it's so good!
The cheese is sour.
And the dough is sweet.
It's a good balance!
I love it!
Me too!
Ohhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Mmm!Mmmm~!
Happiness!
So happy!
Is it good?
Delicious!
Everyone come and eat too!
Ah, ah,
Thank you for the food!
I'm back!
How was it? Surprisingly...
Surprisingly...
Rie-chan was on board.
Make it on the board?
What's that? You call them "furikko"?
I felt like I was attached to her.
That's right.
I used to do that a lot.
I want to be like this.
As for Shinju-san...
It's business as usual.
But...
I didn't miss anything.
It was too much.
There were times when you were even more inept than I was.
I didn't care about the camera.
I didn't put the camera on.
I remember now with a heavy heart.
Here's my card from that time.
A ten-yen coin, please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, I'm doing this. Is it reversible?
Today is the second one. We may do it again.
You're doing the first one? The first one was at a different restaurant with different members.
If the comments are favorable, I'm sure we'll continue.
Don't worry, don't worry. You're so desperate.It's okay, it's okay. You're so desperate.
But it was fun. How was the bread?
It was delicious! It was really good!
I had some myself, and it was really good.
It's so simple, but it's so addictive.
It's so rich! It's so long and delicious!
It was the first time it was in Sendai, so before and after the photo shoot, there were a lot of young people waiting in line to buy it.
There were a lot of young people waiting in line to buy it.
I was surprised at how popular it is.
I hope you'll try it too!
So, this 10 yen bread is sold at the kitchen car.
Please check our website to see when the kitchen car will be here.
You can see when the kitchen car will be here, so I hope you will visit the place on that day and enjoy the atmosphere.
That's all for now.
I hope you will all try the 10 yen bread!
Oh! Briko!
See you again!
Yes, OK!